<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Prayer Reflections]]></title><description><![CDATA[Quotes amidst these times of difficulty.]]></description><link>http://bibanco.deleonanddeleon.com</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 03:12:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Conformity]]></title><description><![CDATA[Sharing today … Quote: Jesus never change. Yet, knowing Him changes everything. Passage: Jesus Christ is the same yesterday, today, and…]]></description><link>http://bibanco.deleonanddeleon.com/conformity/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://bibanco.deleonanddeleon.com/conformity/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 22:40:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Sharing today …&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Quote:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jesus never change. Yet, knowing Him changes everything.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Passage:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jesus Christ is the same yesterday, today, and forever!&lt;br&gt;
[Hebrews 13:8]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Oratio Imperata]]></title><description><![CDATA[Kapatid, In case you haven’t got these prayers on Covid 19 pandemic, sharing to you the 
Oratio Imperata and US Conference of Catholic…]]></description><link>http://bibanco.deleonanddeleon.com/oratio-imperata/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://bibanco.deleonanddeleon.com/oratio-imperata/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 23:40:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Kapatid,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In case you haven’t got these prayers on Covid 19 pandemic, sharing to you the
&lt;strong&gt;Oratio Imperata&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;US Conference of Catholic Bishops (USCB) Prayer of Solidarity&lt;/strong&gt;.
You can include these as you pray the Flores de Mayo Rosary honoring our Blessed Mother.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you and keep safe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Oratio Imperata&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;on the threat from COVID-19&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;God our Father,&lt;br&gt;
We come to you in our need&lt;br&gt;
To ask your protection against the COVID-19 Virus,&lt;br&gt;
That has claimed lives&lt;br&gt;
And has affected many.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We pray for your grace&lt;br&gt;
For the people tasked with studying the nature and cause&lt;br&gt;
Of this virus and its disease&lt;br&gt;
And of stemming the tide of its transmission.&lt;br&gt;
Guide the hands and minds of medical experts&lt;br&gt;
That they may minister to the sick&lt;br&gt;
With competence and compassion,&lt;br&gt;
And of those governments and private agencies&lt;br&gt;
That must find cure and solution to this epidemic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We pray for those afflicted&lt;br&gt;
May they be restored to health soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Grant us the grace&lt;br&gt;
To work for the good of all&lt;br&gt;
And to help those in need.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Grant this through our Lord, Jesus Christ, your Son,&lt;br&gt;
Who lives and reigns with You, in the unity of the Holy Spirit,&lt;br&gt;
God, forever and ever. Amen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Mary Help of all Christians, pray for us.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;St. Raphael the Archangel, pray for us.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;St. Rock, pray for us.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;St. Lorenzo Ruiz, pray for us.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;em&gt;St. Pedro Calungsod, pray for us.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;COVID-19: A Prayer of Solidarity&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For all who have contracted coronavirus,&lt;br&gt;
     We pray for care and healing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those who are particularly vulnerable,&lt;br&gt;
     We pray for safety and protection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For all who experience fear or anxiety,&lt;br&gt;
     We pray for peace of mind and spirit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For affected families who are facing difficult decisions between food on the table or public safety,&lt;br&gt;
     We pray for policies that recognize their plight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those who do not have adequate health insurance,&lt;br&gt;
     We pray that no family will face financial burdens alone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those who are afraid to access care due to immigration status,&lt;br&gt;
     We pray for recognition of the God-given dignity of all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For our brothers and sisters around the world,&lt;br&gt;
     We pray for shared solidarity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For public officials and decisionmakers,&lt;br&gt;
     We pray for wisdom and guidance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Father, during this time may your Church be a sign of hope, comfort and love to all.&lt;br&gt;
     Grant peace.&lt;br&gt;
     Grant comfort.&lt;br&gt;
     Grant healing.&lt;br&gt;
     Be with us, Lord.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amen.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Creation]]></title><description><![CDATA[Sharing to you the framework of creation in the Book of Genesis. Genesis pictures the created world in a state of primeval chaos, submerged…]]></description><link>http://bibanco.deleonanddeleon.com/creation/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://bibanco.deleonanddeleon.com/creation/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 22:40:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Sharing to you the framework of creation in the Book of Genesis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Genesis pictures the created world in a state of primeval chaos, submerged in water &amp;#x26; shrouded in darkness.  It is place unfit for life and habitation.  It conveys this idea as something “without form and void” &lt;em&gt;(Genesis 1:2)&lt;/em&gt;.  These formlessness and emptiness set the stage of creation in two phases: on days 1-2-3 God forms the world into its temporal &amp;#x26; spatial dimensions; and on days 4-5-6 He fills the world with its designated rulers.  Genesis thus arranges the creation account in symmetrical fashion, with the first three days corresponding to the second three days.  The seventh days stands apart as the day when God rested.  Inherent in this literary format is the message that the cosmos, in its artistic design and orderliness, bears witness to the consummate wisdom of the Creator &lt;em&gt;(see Psalm 19:1, Wisdom 13:5, Romans 1:20)&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;FROM FORMLESSNESS:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Day 1  Day &amp;#x26; Night  &lt;em&gt;(Genesis 1:3-5;)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Day 2  Sea &amp;#x26; Sky    &lt;em&gt;(Geneses 1:6-8)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Day 3  Land &amp;#x26; Vegetation   &lt;em&gt;(Genesis 1:9-13)&lt;/em&gt;    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;FROM EMPTINESS (VOID):&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Day 4  Sun, Moon, Stars   &lt;em&gt;(Genesis 1:14-19)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Day 5  Fish &amp;#x26; Birds   &lt;em&gt;(Genesis 1:20-23)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Day 6  Man &amp;#x26; Animals   &lt;em&gt;(Genesis 1:24-31)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Day 7  The Sabbath Rest   (Genesis 2:1-3)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Sabbath which is set apart for the worship of God and the contemplation of His work, is a sign of His covenant with creation.  God sanctified the seventh day that work is ordered to worship, lest man become slave to his labor and fail to acknowledge his total dependence on the Lord (see &lt;strong&gt;Catechism of the Catholic Church (CCC) paragraphs 347, 2175-76&lt;/strong&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;[Please read the passages in your Bibles/Catechism as indicated]&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you and you can share this email.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;References:&lt;br&gt;
Catholic Bible Revised Standard Version&lt;br&gt;
Ignatius Catholic Study Bible&lt;br&gt;
Catechism of the Catholic Church (CCC)  &lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Doctors of the Church]]></title><description><![CDATA[As of now there are 33 Doctors of the Church. Today the word doctor would probably those persons who are caring for physical or mental…]]></description><link>http://bibanco.deleonanddeleon.com/doctors-church/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://bibanco.deleonanddeleon.com/doctors-church/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2020 22:40:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;As of now there are 33 Doctors of the Church.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today the word doctor would probably those persons who are caring for physical or mental health.  The term “doctor” originally derived from the Latin word &lt;em&gt;“docere”&lt;/em&gt; meaning &lt;em&gt;“to teach”&lt;/em&gt;.  It designated anyone whose knowledge qualified to teach and not necessarily one who is skilled caring for human health.  Such “doctors” were experts in promoting another kind of health --- the health of the soul and spirit which comes from knowing the truth &lt;em&gt;[John 8:32 And you shall know the truth, and the truth shall make you free;  John 14:6  I am the way, the truth, and the life]&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;“Doctors of the Church”&lt;/strong&gt; are people who have seen the glory of Jesus Christ, full of grace &amp;#x26; truth &lt;em&gt;[John 18:37-38  Jesus said “for this I have come into the world, to bear witness to the truth. Every one who is of the truth hears my voice”. Pilate said to him, what is truth?]&lt;/em&gt;.  In addition, by cooperating with God’s special graces and employing their unique intellectual &amp;#x26; pedagogical (education &amp;#x26; learning) gifts, they succeeded in an outstanding way in communicating the truth they have contemplated in Jesus.  As such, they are eminent teachers, their teachings bring health to the human heart and soul.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Who are these doctors?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;St Athanasius&lt;/strong&gt; - Father of Orthodoxy, Defender of Christianity in the East, 297-373 AD (Feast day May 2)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;St Ephrem&lt;/strong&gt; - Father of Hymnody,  306-373 AD  (Feast day June 9)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;St Cyril of Jerusalem&lt;/strong&gt; - Doctor of Catechism, 315-386 AD  (Feast day March 18)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;St Hilary of Poitiers&lt;/strong&gt; - Defender of Christianity in the West,  315-368 AD  (Feast day January 13) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;St Gregory Nazianzen&lt;/strong&gt; - The Theologian,  329-386 AD  (Feast day January 2)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;St Basil the Great&lt;/strong&gt; - Father of Eastern Monasticism,  329-379 AD  (Feast day January 2)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;St Ambrose&lt;/strong&gt; - Patron of the Veneration of Mary,  340-397 AD  (Feast day December 7)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;St Jerome&lt;/strong&gt; - Father of Biblical Science,  342-420 AD  (Feast day September 30)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;St John Chrysostom&lt;/strong&gt; - Doctor of the Eucharist,  347-407 AD  (Feast day September 13)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;St Augustine&lt;/strong&gt; - Doctor of Grace,  354-430 AD  (Feast day August 28)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;St Cyril of Alexandra&lt;/strong&gt; - Doctor of the Incarnation,  376-444 AD  (Feast day June 27)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pope St Leo the Great&lt;/strong&gt; - Doctor of the Unity of the Church,  400-450 AD (Feast day November 10)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;St Peter Chrysologus&lt;/strong&gt; - The Golden-Worded  406-450 AD  (Feast day July 30)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pope St Gregory the Great&lt;/strong&gt; - The Greatest of the Great,  540-604 AD  (Feast day September 3)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;St Isidore of Seville&lt;/strong&gt; - Schoolmaster of the Middle Ages,  560-636 AD  (Feast day April 4)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;St Bede the Venerable&lt;/strong&gt; - Father of English History,  673-735 AD  (Feast day May 25)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;St John Damascene&lt;/strong&gt; - Doctor of Assumption and Christian Art,  676-749 AD  (Feast day December 4)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;St Peter Damian&lt;/strong&gt; - Monitor of the Popes,  1007-1072 AD  (Feast day February 21)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;St Anselm&lt;/strong&gt; - Father of Scholasticism,  1033-1109 AD  (Feast day April 21)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;St Bernard of Clairvauz&lt;/strong&gt; - The Mellifluous Doctor, 1090-1153 AD  (Feast day August 20)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;St Anthony the Padua&lt;/strong&gt; - Doctor of the Gospel,  1195-1231 AD  (Feast day June 13)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;St Albert the Great&lt;/strong&gt; - The Universal Doctor,  1206-1231 AD  (Feast day November 15) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;St Bonaventure&lt;/strong&gt; - The Seraphic Doctor,  1221-1274 AD  (Feast day July 15)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;St Thomas Aquinas&lt;/strong&gt; - The Angelic Doctor,  1225-1274 AD  (Feast day January 28)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;St Catherine of Siena&lt;/strong&gt; - Mystic of Incarnate Word,  1347-1380 AD  (Feast day April 29)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;St Theresa of Avila&lt;/strong&gt; - Doctor of Prayer,  1515-1582 AD  (Feast day October 15)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;St Peter Canisius&lt;/strong&gt; - Doctor of Catechism,  1521-1597 AD  (Feast day April 27)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;St Robert Bellarmine&lt;/strong&gt; - Prince of Apologists,  1542-1621 AD  (Feast day September 17)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;St John of the Cross&lt;/strong&gt; - Doctor of Mystical Theology,  1542-1591 AD  (Feast day  December 14)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;St Lawrence of Brindisi&lt;/strong&gt; - The Apostolic Doctor,  1559-1619 AD  (Feast day July 21)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;St Francis de Sales&lt;/strong&gt; - The Gentleman Doctor,  1567-1622 AD  (Feast day January 24)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;St Alphonsus Liguori&lt;/strong&gt; - Prince of Moralists,  1696-1787 AD  Feast day August 1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;St Therese of Lisieux&lt;/strong&gt; - Doctor of of the Little Way, Doctor of Merciful Love,  1873-1897 AD  (Feast day Oct 1)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Priestly Ministry and the Essentials of Christian Discipleship in the Time of Coronavirus]]></title><description><![CDATA[Sharing to you this video interview (approx 30 min) with this covid 19
pandemic situation in relation to our Catholic faith   … The Priestly…]]></description><link>http://bibanco.deleonanddeleon.com/priestly-ministry/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://bibanco.deleonanddeleon.com/priestly-ministry/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 22:40:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Sharing to you this video interview (approx 30 min) with this covid 19
pandemic situation in relation to our Catholic faith   …&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://ebook.wordonfire.org/interviewwithfrbritton&quot;&gt;The Priestly Ministry and the Essentials of Christian Discipleship…&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Saint Catherine of Siena]]></title><description><![CDATA[April 29th is the feast day of St Catherine of Siena.  She is one of the Doctors of the Church, patroness of Italy, mystic, woman of action…]]></description><link>http://bibanco.deleonanddeleon.com/st-catherine-siena/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://bibanco.deleonanddeleon.com/st-catherine-siena/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 22:40:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;April 29th is the feast day of &lt;strong&gt;St Catherine of Siena&lt;/strong&gt;.  She is one of the Doctors of the Church, patroness of Italy, mystic, woman of action, heroine against overwhelming odds, persuaded Pope Gregory XI to leave &lt;em&gt;Avignon&lt;/em&gt; and return to Rome.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Catherine Benincasa is the youngest of the 25 children of a prosperous Sienese wool-dyer.  She rejected marriage and religious life but enamored of consecrated virginity.  At sixteen, she became a Dominican tertiary but continued to live at home.  For three years she left her room only for Mass and Confession.  Her mortification reached the point where she would manage on a spoonful of herbs and few hours of sleep a day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At nineteen, after the experience of Christ placing a ring on her finger, visible only to herself, she resumed normal family life and began to care for the sick &amp;#x26; the poor.  Soon people were attracted by the charm of Catherine’s human &amp;#x26; supernatural qualities … her gaiety, religious fervor, social involvement, unconventionality, loyalty to the church, etc.  She wrote, “their concern was to remove hatred from people’s heart and bring them to peace with Christ crucified and their neighbors”.  At twenty-eight she received the stigmata, which also remained invisible to others until her death.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She had become all love for God and neighbor, ecstasies, peace missions, letters to help others and care for the ills of the church.  Infused wisdom and the gift of exhortation were her special charisms.  She took 23 of her group on the three month’s historic embassy to Avignon.  Reforms she saw would come not with war but with peace and quite, with the humble &amp;#x26; continuous prayers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She died in Rome at the age of thirty three sealing her activities with this offer of her life:
&lt;em&gt;“O eternal God, receive the sacrifice of my life for this mystical body of holy Church.  I have nothing to give but what you have given me.  Take my heart, therefore, and press it to the face of this spouse.”&lt;/em&gt;   &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;[&lt;strong&gt;Avignon&lt;/strong&gt; is a city in southeastern France where once the seat of the pope during 1309-1377. In some of those years, the Church had even two popes, one in Avignon and one in Rome.  St Catherine was instrumental of having Pope Gregory XI leave Avignon &amp;#x26; ended the confusion and returned the proper papal seat to Rome].&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(Reference:  Lives of the Saints by Fr Augustine Kalberer OSB.)&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Reconnect]]></title><description><![CDATA[Kapatid, We will share some quotes amidst this time of difficulties & concerns. One of 
the areas of hope is the Words of our Redeemer that…]]></description><link>http://bibanco.deleonanddeleon.com/reconnect/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://bibanco.deleonanddeleon.com/reconnect/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 22:40:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Kapatid,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will share some quotes amidst this time of difficulties &amp;#x26; concerns. One of
the areas of hope is the Words of our Redeemer that we can always cling on.&lt;br&gt;
Please continue to pray …&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Quote:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;‘PEACE  …  it’s just a prayer away.’&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Passage:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do not be anxious about anything, but in everything, by prayer &amp;#x26; petition,
with thanksgiving, present your request to God.  And the &gt; peace of God,
which surpasses all understanding, will guard your hearts and your minds
in Christ Jesus.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Philippians 4:6-7&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Peace be with you and your loved ones …&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dennis &amp;#x26; Bing B.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Psalm 91]]></title><description><![CDATA[Sharing to you Psalm 91 (Security under God’s Protection).
This is appropriate in this time of uncertainty, yet we know 
that God will…]]></description><link>http://bibanco.deleonanddeleon.com/psalm91/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://bibanco.deleonanddeleon.com/psalm91/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 22:40:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Sharing to you Psalm 91 &lt;em&gt;(Security under God’s Protection)&lt;/em&gt;.
This is appropriate in this time of uncertainty, yet we know
that God will protect us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You who dwell in the shadow of the Most High, who abide in the shadow of the Almighty.
Say to the Lord, my refuge &amp;#x26; fortress, my God in whom I trust.  God will rescue you from the
fowler’s snare, from the destroying plague, will shelter you with pinions, spread wings that
you may take refuge; God’s faithfulness is a protecting shield.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You shall not fear the terror of the night nor the arrow that flies by day, nor the pestilence
that roams in darkness, nor the plague that ravages at noon.  Though a thousand fall at your
side, ten thousand at your right hand, near you it shall not come.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You need simply watch; the punishment of the wicked you shall see.  You have the Lord for
your refuge; you have made the Most High your stronghold.  No evil shall befall you,
no affliction come near your tent.  For God commands the angels to guard you in your ways.
With their hands they shall support you, lest you strike your foot against a strong.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You shall tread upon the asp and the vipers, trample the lion and the dragon.  Whoever clings
to me I will deliver; whoever knows my name I will set on high.  All who call upon me I will
answer; I will be with them in distress; I will deliver them and give them honor.
Will length of days I will satisfy them and show them my saving power.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See if you can also sing &lt;strong&gt;“On Eagles Wings”&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Glory be to the Father, and to the Son, and to the Holy Spirit; as it was in the
beginning, is now, and ever shall be, world with out end”.  Amen.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>