<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Prayer Reflections]]></title><description><![CDATA[Quotes amidst these times of difficulty.]]></description><link>http://bibanco.deleonanddeleon.com</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 17:00:14 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Priestly Ministry and the Essentials of Christian Discipleship in the Time of Coronavirus]]></title><description><![CDATA[Sharing to you this video interview (approx 30 min) with this covid 19
pandemic situation in relation to our Catholic faith   … The Priestly…]]></description><link>http://bibanco.deleonanddeleon.com/priestly-ministry/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://bibanco.deleonanddeleon.com/priestly-ministry/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 22:40:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Sharing to you this video interview (approx 30 min) with this covid 19
pandemic situation in relation to our Catholic faith   …&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://ebook.wordonfire.org/interviewwithfrbritton&quot;&gt;The Priestly Ministry and the Essentials of Christian Discipleship…&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Reconnect]]></title><description><![CDATA[Kapatid, We will share some quotes amidst this time of difficulties & concerns. One of 
the areas of hope is the Words of our Redeemer that…]]></description><link>http://bibanco.deleonanddeleon.com/reconnect/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://bibanco.deleonanddeleon.com/reconnect/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 22:40:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Kapatid,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will share some quotes amidst this time of difficulties &amp;#x26; concerns. One of
the areas of hope is the Words of our Redeemer that we can always cling on.&lt;br&gt;
Please continue to pray …&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Quote:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;‘PEACE  …  it’s just a prayer away.’&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Passage:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do not be anxious about anything, but in everything, by prayer &amp;#x26; petition,
with thanksgiving, present your request to God.  And the &gt; peace of God,
which surpasses all understanding, will guard your hearts and your minds
in Christ Jesus.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Philippians 4:6-7&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Peace be with you and your loved ones …&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dennis &amp;#x26; Bing B.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Psalm 91]]></title><description><![CDATA[Sharing to you Psalm 91 (Security under God’s Protection).
This is appropriate in this time of uncertainty, yet we know 
that God will…]]></description><link>http://bibanco.deleonanddeleon.com/psalm91/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://bibanco.deleonanddeleon.com/psalm91/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 22:40:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Sharing to you Psalm 91 &lt;em&gt;(Security under God’s Protection)&lt;/em&gt;.
This is appropriate in this time of uncertainty, yet we know
that God will protect us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You who dwell in the shadow of the Most High, who abide in the shadow of the Almighty.
Say to the Lord, my refuge &amp;#x26; fortress, my God in whom I trust.  God will rescue you from the
fowler’s snare, from the destroying plague, will shelter you with pinions, spread wings that
you may take refuge; God’s faithfulness is a protecting shield.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You shall not fear the terror of the night nor the arrow that flies by day, nor the pestilence
that roams in darkness, nor the plague that ravages at noon.  Though a thousand fall at your
side, ten thousand at your right hand, near you it shall not come.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You need simply watch; the punishment of the wicked you shall see.  You have the Lord for
your refuge; you have made the Most High your stronghold.  No evil shall befall you,
no affliction come near your tent.  For God commands the angels to guard you in your ways.
With their hands they shall support you, lest you strike your foot against a strong.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You shall tread upon the asp and the vipers, trample the lion and the dragon.  Whoever clings
to me I will deliver; whoever knows my name I will set on high.  All who call upon me I will
answer; I will be with them in distress; I will deliver them and give them honor.
Will length of days I will satisfy them and show them my saving power.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See if you can also sing &lt;strong&gt;“On Eagles Wings”&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Glory be to the Father, and to the Son, and to the Holy Spirit; as it was in the
beginning, is now, and ever shall be, world with out end”.  Amen.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>